<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Europe Travels</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="category_landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="category_history">History</string>
    <string name="category_dining">Dining</string>
    <string name="category_activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="louvre_museum">This museum holds enough paintings that you will have to spend multiple days even if you spent only 3 seconds per painting! It also houses the Mona Lisa painting.</string>
    <string name="swiss_tunnels">The mountains and tunnels gives Switzerland great control of what goes in and out of the country.  Major transportation paths such as the tunnels, bridges, or railways are rigged with explosives in the scenario that they are attacked by invaders.</string>
    <string name="notre_dame">A medieval Catholic church in Paris, and acts as the geographical center of Paris.</string>
    <string name="swiss_jungfraujoch">Take a train ride to enjoy the view from the top of this mountain, also dubbed the \'Top of Europe.\'  Very famous sight to see, especially for people that have not experienced a white Christmas!</string>
    <string name="montmarte_tour">There are some free walking tours available in Paris that are funded by tips.  Montmarte was a nice tour that shows some history of street arts around the area, including the \'Wall of Love\' which displays multiple ways of saying \'I love you.\'</string>
    <string name="rome_tour">This walking tour shows you the famous landmarks within Rome, including the Spanish Steps, Trevi Fountain, and the Colisseum.  Rome is pretty well structured for tourists that all these landmarks are just a short 5 minute walk from each other.</string>
    <string name="venice_restaurant">Restaurant found in the streets of Venice that serves very delicious seafood! Staff was very friendly and even included appetizers and desserts with the meals.</string>
    <string name="munich_restaurant">Restaurant and beer hall in Munich with great beer!  Atmosphere was somewhat noisy open area, but very enjoyable for a beer hall.</string>
    <string name="eiffel_tower">You cannot visit Paris without seeing this main attraction!  Especially looks lovely at night time!</string>
    <string name="vatican_city">The headquarters for the Roman Catholic Church. This is the smallest country in the world and is completely surrounded by the borders of Italy.</string>
    <string name="swiss_alps">These mountains are a must if you ever stop by Switzerland. They are just so refreshing to look at and was definitely an amazing experience.</string>
</resources>
